Blessed
be the name of our shine.
be the name of the Lord. The shame of
the night.
Blessed
be the name of the Lord
of the night.
Blessed
be the name of the Lord.
Lift it up.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
of the Lord.
Blessed be the name.
We worship you Lord.
Blessed be your name Jesus.
Blessed be your name. Bless
be name.
Blessed be your name.
Somebody just make me.
We worship you
in the name of
Heat. Heat.
Lift your eyes.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Yeah.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat
up here.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Yeah.
Heat.
me.
I know.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Blessed be the name of the Lord.
Heat.
Yeah. Heat.
Bless
the name of the Lord.
Blessed
be the name of the Lord.
name
from Asia to Africa
be your name my God
America to Europe blessed be
blessed be your name
Antarctica we sing blessed
in the name of
Male and female will say bless
in the name of the Lord.
Young and old we cry out bless
family altars. We cry out bless
our churches. We cry out blessed be the
children. We cry out.
We cry out. Bless
revival. We break up those are
our fathers we pray. Our waters with
fire
on the mountain in the valley.
Somebody just make me
Yeah.
Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat up
here.
Yeah. Heat.
Hey,
nation to nation.
Mother,
family to family,
territory to territory. Oh.
Heat.
Heat up here.
Heat. Heat.
Yeah. Heat.
Yeah.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
family altars are coming back. I'm
telling
his glory is here.